caplay.com 2012-05-24

# PrivacyAbout -Caplay | Play it Immediately

Welcome to CAPLAY.com!  

CAPLAY.com believes that maintaining and preserving the privacy of user data is of the utmost importance. This Privacy Policy represents a committed effort to safeguard the security of the limited user information that is collected and retained on our servers. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through CAPLAY.com and not to information collected offline or to information you may provide to any third-party sites to which CAPLAY.com may link, except as expressly provided herein.  

**Information We Collect**

There are two kinds of information that CAPLAY.com can obtain about you: “Anonymous Information” and “Personally Identifiable Information.”

“Anonymous Information” consists of non-personally-identifiable data, such as your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address or domain, or information about your usage on CAPLAY.com that is used for administrative purposes only. An Internet protocol ("IP") address is the unique number assigned to your server or Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). CAPLAY.com may track such IP addresses for system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to report aggregate information to our advertisers, corporate affiliates and consultants, and to third parties that perform particular services on our behalf, or to prevent our servers from being abused.

“Personally Identifiable Information” may include your name, home address, phone number, and/or e-mail address. We do not require this information to gain access to our sites, however, you will not be able to utilize certain products, services, or features that require registration or receive materials such as newsletters unless such information is provided.

When we collect Personally Identifiable Information from you, you will have the opportunity to “opt in” to receive email or other digital communications from us and/or our business partners.

If you have submitted your personal information to **  CAPLAY**.com, you may correct, amend or delete the Personally Identifiable Information maintained on file about you if it is incorrect.

In all cases, we will only use your information as permitted by law. Notwithstanding any other provision of this Privacy Policy, however, we may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to others if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property; (c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site; or (d) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. Please note that we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Use of “Cookies”**

Cookies are a feature of your Web browser that allows Web sites to transfer bits of information to your computer for record-keeping purposes.  CAPLAY.com use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit CAPLAY.com. In addition, CAPLAY may use cookies to retrieve user information for promotional, marketing, or security purposes.

**Disclosure of Information through Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses, and in so doing, acquire customer information. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. Similarly, in the event that a portion or all of CAPLAY.com's assets are sold or transferred to a third party, customer information (including your email address) would likely be one of the transferred business assets.

**Third Party Web Sites**

**CAPLAY**.com contains links to third-party Web sites not owned or controlled by  **CAPLAY**.com. **  CAPLAY**.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party Web sites. Inclusion of any linked Web site on CAPLAY.com does not imply or express an approval or endorsement of the linked Web site by us, or of any of the content, opinions, products or services provided on these Web sites. Even if an affiliation exists between CAPLAY.com and a third-party Web site, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a Web site via a link from one of our Sites, we encourage you to consult that Web site's privacy policy before providing any personal information, and whenever interacting with any such Web site.

**Security**

CAPLAY.com has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Security of information communicated by or to us over the Internet is of utmost concern to us; however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that your email, like most, if not all, unencrypted Internet communications, may potentially be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. While we strive to protect your personal information, CAPLAY.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Once we receive your transmission, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our internal systems. Depending on the nature of the inquiry, your communication may be discarded or archived.

**Policy Regarding Minors**

Children should always ask parents before providing any personal information online. No information should be submitted to or posted on CAPLAY.com by any minor (a person under 18 years of age) without the consent of a parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, we do not knowingly provide any Personally Identifiable Information about minors, regardless of its source, nor is this information knowingly used by CAPLAY.com for any marketing or promotional purposes. Minors are not eligible to participate in contests.  
CAPLAY.com abides by the Children Online Privacy Protection Act. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from any child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete this information from our database as quickly as reasonably possible. If you believe that any Site has collected any information about anyone under 13, please contact CAPLAY.com's Site Administrator via postal mail or email at one of the addresses listed below.

**Limitation of Liability**

****CAPLAY.com**  provides the information, services and products on this web sites “as is” without warranties of any kind. you agree that CAPLAY.com shall not be responsible for any content found on our forums, that any downloading of materials found on or through  **CAPLAY.com**  forums is done at your own risk, and that  **CAPLAY.com**  is not responsible for unsolicited communications that arise from your postings.  **CAPLAY.com**  shall not be responsible in any manner for the acts of any third party, including witout limitation, any third party ad network.**

 ****

**Consent and Modifications to this Privacy Statement**

CAPLAY.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. By using CAPLAY.com and/or participating in the activities of CAPLAY.com Community, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with this Privacy Statement, please do not disclose any personal information through our site. CAPLAY.com may modify this Privacy Statement at any time, at its discretion, and modifications are effective upon being posted on this the applicable Site. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Statement periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.

**What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?**

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities with restricted access, and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to CAPLAY.com employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the CAPLAY.com Features. All CAPLAY.com personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the CAPLAY.com Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.  

**Notification of Changes**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on this page.

**Contacting CAPLAY.com**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement you may contact us at: (NEEDS LINK)  

**This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 1, 2010 and supersedes all earlier versions of our Privacy Policy**
